[Music]
[Applause]
good morning everyone it's aya Maki
today we're gonna be making bail gonna
dog on Oklahoma coffee thought I wanna
call here it's been anything on the
Internet
well I've seen it on an internet for
about two months now so I'm kind of late
but better late than never
spoiler alert this video is literally
going to be me just mixing these
ingredients together so if you have
better things to do which studies have
shown that 99.9 percent of the human
population usually have better things to
do than to watch me do anything of any
sort no hard feelings
go do what you have to do but for those
of you that decide to stay there may
come a day when you need something from
me and when that day comes I will
remember this very moment and the
sacrifices you have made for me all
right let's make it the ingredients are
actually very simple there's absolutely
no way you can mess this up all you need
is instant coffee milk hot water and
sugar I don't have sugar but I do have
honey it's basically the same thing I
don't have hot water but I have cold
water it's close enough I don't have a
measuring spoon but I do have this
Jewish amatsu gigantic spoon it's
actually better than a measuring cup
also I don't have an electric mixer but
I have my hand and mixer so what more do
you need science has taken us too far
perhaps we have forgotten that we have
hands everything is supposed to be like
a 1 1 1 ratio response it it's not it
but if they want to sponsor me okay keep
one scoop of this instant coffee in oh
that's ok it's gonna evaporate so
all right sugar
also known as honey are you are you okay
down there
hello that's enough I'm almost done we
just have to mix this I really don't
like this wall because they see my
reflection on it and it makes me think
about what I'm doing to myself if I
bleach my eyebrows well you guys be
there for me yeah thanks the amount of
stress this is giving me right now is
just oh that's that's too okay that's
too much do you guys see how much my
roots have gone my manager told me that
I'm not allowed to change how I look
without their permission
but my body is naturally changing how I
look there for making me break company
policies I'm gonna get fired
is this everybody's new way of saying
that they hate themselves no matter how
much time you have during this
quarantine this is not worth it this
figure is probably gonna be like three
minutes but I've been taking this for 50
minutes now it's guys I think it's done
[Music]
I think I actually made it and it's a
happy setting up for my tea party do you
see that Oh cute just piece of milk is
mixing this whole thing to feed its
goodness
[Music]
mmm-mmm-mmm like happiness mixed with
happiness I take back what I said about
this not being worth your time this is
definitely worth your time drop
everything what you're doing your career
over this is what your life should be
revolving around right now I can't tell
if it's actually good or if it's good
because I made it this is the best thing
I've ever made in my life I can say that
without hurting anybody because I don't
have any kids I'm sick they're watching
hey guys
[Music]
you