Good morning everyone it's Sally Amaki
Today's video is going to be with my member Ruri Umino
if a girl born and raised in America and a girl born and raised in Japan took a job interview, we're pretty sure it's gonna be different so today we tried it out.
The jokes I made in Japanese don't really translate well in english but I'm putting subtitles anyway
LET'S GO
Please Introduce yourself
My name is Ruri Umino. I've worked as a voice actor and an idol in my past job
therefore I know the importance of communicating with people through my words and body language
and I believe that doing so is my speciality.
Thank you for giving me your time of day today
IDK how to translate YOROSHIKUONEGAISHIMASU
EXCUSE ME I'M SO SORRY I'M LATE
I'm Sally Amaki nice to meet you
WAIT JUST LISTEN. On my way over here, I saw an old lady drowning in the river and
I'm the type that can't leave those people behind so it took me some time to help her
But because you all patiently waited for me, another life was saved so thank you so much for that
So, shall we begin?
Do you have any management  experience?
I do not have any management experience but I did have somebody that did during my previous job
therefore, I'm aware of what is required for the job.
Yes. I mean all my life I've been supported, in other words managed, by those around me
but ever since I realized that the only one who is capable of managing me is myself,
I've been my very own manager.
How would those around you rate you?
Many people tell me that I have the ability to take action quite fast. I'm the type of person who would start working the second I come up with something
Therefore, if I get into this company, I would like to make use of those qualities of mine and bring in new ideas to the company
Okay well my friends and family don't really 'rate' people with numbers cuz that's rude so it's kinda hard to answer your question
but I get all As on my report card and my name's on the Dean's list too so if we're talking numbers, you can say the results come out to say that I'm perfect
What were you doing during the time you had off after quitting your previous job?
I contacted my previous manager to learn the basics of the job to prepare myself
I also traveled to places I've never gone to to reflect on myself.
I went on a journey to find myself
I believe it was around a year ago, as I was walking around Southeast Asia, I looked down and saw my own shadow spreading from my toes into the wilderness.
The moment I saw that shadow, I felt as if I found myself.
I've been all around the world trying to find myself only to realize that I've been here all along. My shadow here proves my existence in this world.
How would you finish a job you find to be boring?
I've never found a job to be boring. I finish each job knowing that it all makes me grow as a person.
I'd probably just be like
but do it anyway
What do you think this industry would be like in 10 years?
Compared to 10 years ago, there are so many more jobs that allow for people to be in the spotlight. For instance youtubers and virtual youtubers.
Therefore, 10years from now I believe that there will be even more opportunities for people in show business and so along with that, more managers would be required for them.
Well the future's going to change depending on you hiring me or not.
If you don't hire me, I can see that this company won't be able to keep up with the entertainment business and the changes they go through every 5 seconds.
If I'm here, I can globalize this whole company and make it be known worldwide.
This job is hard for both men and women, would you be able to handle that?
If you will hire me, I promise that I will finish every job.
I'll have a strong mentality and try my very best at everything.
Well if it's hard for both men and women, what is there to be scared of? We'll all just go down together as a whole. TEAMWORK yay
When do you find your job rewarding?
It's not like I work in hopes of getting praised but whenever people tell me 'thank you' or 'good job' it pushes me to keep trying hard.
PAYDAY
Do you have any questions for us?
What position do you want to play in this industry in the future?
Yea uh, when should I start?